<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Start Here on Pamela Wang</title>
    <link>https://caffa.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Start Here on Pamela Wang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://caffa.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Currently I am an AI 🎮 grad student in Singapore. I spend my free time reading webnovels and fanfics 📚 + trying to optimize my productivity system in Obsidian.
TODO More indepth about me :) - I would like something like https://aliabdaal.com/about/ for layout of what I want this page to be like </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>customizing our setup has hidden costs</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-customizing-our-setup-has-hidden-costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-customizing-our-setup-has-hidden-costs/</guid>
      <description>source::
if we consider customization = slow changes of design till something is exactly as you like it
Then as you customize, your baseline moves from 3 to 5 to 8, so it is hard to get used to the default setup (3).
E.g. Default setup = Macbook You add &amp;ldquo;Multiple monitors&amp;rdquo; = + 2 Comfort and Functionality You add &amp;ldquo;Shortcuts&amp;rdquo; = + 1 Speed and Functionality You add &amp;ldquo;Moonlander&amp;rdquo; = + 2 Comfort and Speed You add &amp;ldquo;MOBA Mouse&amp;rdquo; = + 1 Comfort and Effectiveness</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>different mask you hold for every situation</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-different-mask-you-hold-for-every-situation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-different-mask-you-hold-for-every-situation/</guid>
      <description>source::
I think people have different masks for every person that they talk to, or groups of people
family work ppl alone by myself even within groups, there are subgroups (family - brothers, or parents) Some aspects of yourself are magnified, behaviour changes to what is appropriate for the situation (performative?). do people really have personalities, what even is a personality?
It might be conscious on some parts but I think switching between masks is more of a subconscious behaviour cued by</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>digital nomad</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-digital-nomad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-digital-nomad/</guid>
      <description>source:: Deep Dive Podcast Ali Abdaal - Digital Nomad
Definition Someone who travels as part of their lifestyle, more of having multiple home bases in a few countries that they move between a few times a year.
Only really possible for remote work because they won&amp;rsquo;t be going in to the office.
Problems Sounds like something I would like to try but also note the difficulties inherent in this:
Visa to be allowed to stay in another country constantly having to move = burden in some cases the burden of moving your things - might be better as a minimalist who does not have that many possessions but realistically I am a tech gadget hoarder and general accumulator of lots of random things I can&amp;rsquo;t bear to throw away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>do humans have fundamental nature?</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-do-humans-have-fundamental-nature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-do-humans-have-fundamental-nature/</guid>
      <description>source::
What is fundamental?
Genetics determine who you are? but say your &amp;lsquo;soul&amp;rsquo; is the same but you were born to different partents Nature vs Nurture tho, Nurture plays a big part in who you are although Nature affects who you are too </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>do people really have personalities</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-do-people-really-have-personalities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-do-people-really-have-personalities/</guid>
      <description>source::
I feel like I act differently at different times, places and situations. Largely depending on my energy levels. So what even is a personality.
I think dissociative identity disorder is a really good example of the existence of personalities, but then most of the alters seem to have different pasts (Dissociadid at least?) so I guess it is more of different pasts shape you differently?
My question is
Is personality intrinsic?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>home is the most comfortable place</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-home-is-the-most-comfortable-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-home-is-the-most-comfortable-place/</guid>
      <description>source::
For most people, home should be the most comfortable place
since you can customize it to your liking and having control over your personal space is important. if we consider customization = slow changes of design till something is exactly as you like it, although preferences shift over time or we have too many conflicting desires so things can never be perfectly as you would like them to be you can do whatever you want when you are at home, because in public there is a need to act properly Examples of ways you can customize your home</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I learn things</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-how-i-learn-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-how-i-learn-things/</guid>
      <description>So currently, I learn things via
theory break it down beginner guides how other people use this thing (e.g. da vinci resolve tips and training videos) practice try a small project (e.g. renpy visual novels) create something cute / useful (e.g. bitbar script for youtube stats) memorization anki - spaced repetition (the videos on how to do anki efficiently by med students using AnKing Deck are chef&amp;rsquo;s kiss) useful for things that are just lots of information and definitions when you need a lot of basic info to understand what you are reading (papers) also for remembering summaries of papers (so I can discuss with other people in my lab) As a way to revisit zettels (there are a few different ways to &amp;lsquo;see random note&amp;rsquo; or export from obsidian to anki) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>in public there is a need to act properly</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-in-public-there-is-a-need-to-act-properly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-in-public-there-is-a-need-to-act-properly/</guid>
      <description>source::
The idea that there is a different mask you hold for every situation and the public mask is one that adheres to social norms like
sit without slouching, sit with your legs closed, do not put your legs on another chair cover your mouth when you yawn, say excuse me when you sneeze do not listen to music without headphones People may not choose to adhere to these behaviours but there is general pressure to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>minimalist</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-minimalist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-minimalist/</guid>
      <description>source::
Be a minimalist. Kill your darlings. Elizabeth Filips
Living with minimal possessions, usually only the few things you really value.
Somewhat similar to only keep what sparks joy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my life goal is to be a hermit</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-my-life-goal-is-to-be-a-hermit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-my-life-goal-is-to-be-a-hermit/</guid>
      <description>source::
I feel like I would really enjoy staying at home for the rest of my life (occassionally leaving for walks and swimming unless I get an estate big enough for both), because
home is the most comfortable place Covid has showed me that I don&amp;rsquo;t like &amp;ldquo;not being able to leave home&amp;rdquo; because there is this feeling of freedom being restricted and then the only thing I want to do is to leave the house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My List of Questions</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-my-list-of-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-my-list-of-questions/</guid>
      <description>Somewhat like the idea of My 12 Favourite Questions but instead this is a list of every question I have that I plan on working through, and the answers I found for each (usually sent to [ Zettel Inbox](Z%20-%20Zettel%20Inbox.md))</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nurture plays a big part in who you are</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-nurture-plays-a-big-part-in-who-you-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-nurture-plays-a-big-part-in-who-you-are/</guid>
      <description>source::
We are affected by the influences around us, because they shape our beliefs and identity, and thus who we are and also our future interactions.
Chat with Mervin Walk - culture 2022-06-13 I had an interesting discussion with my brother on this actually, What is culture, how beliefs → identity and also back?
Something like this instead? Tu WeiMing Confucian Circles of Concern models self, family, others are concentric circles that interact with each other?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>only keep what sparks joy</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-only-keep-what-sparks-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-only-keep-what-sparks-joy/</guid>
      <description>source::
marie kondo on decluttering</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>people have special needs beyond the basics</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-people-have-special-needs-beyond-the-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-people-have-special-needs-beyond-the-basics/</guid>
      <description>source::
There is the idea of fundamental needs / basic rights, that have mostly been encoded into law, e.g. right to health care, need food to live, and even somewhat quantified (3 weeks without food, 3 days without water, 3 hours without shelter, 3 mins without air not entirely accurate but it gives a general picture)
A good representation of standard needs is something like maslow hierarchy of needs
although this is also subject to changes between generations of people and models can only approximate the truth so it is not like the perfect list of needs either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>remote work</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-remote-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-remote-work/</guid>
      <description>source::
There are different levels of remote work, GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Guide to All-Remote as defined by gitlab Article Source - The Five Levels of Remote Work — and Why You’re Probably at Level 2
Remote work is mainly the idea that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be there in person, you can work from anywhere in the world, including your own home.
Benefits:
personal not wasting time on travel business not having to rent an office space Problems:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rituals that doctors do</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-rituals-that-doctors-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-rituals-that-doctors-do/</guid>
      <description>source::
Sometime during my university, in one of the humanities classes, I read about &amp;lsquo;rituals&amp;rsquo; people have, not religious rituals but more of like tiny acts people do before they do stuff.
An example was how doctors had their own &amp;lsquo;rituals&amp;rsquo; for washing their hands before surgery, or how athletes (sports competition ppl specifically?) would do the same actions everytime before they play.
It puts you in the correct state of mind to do the thing, sorta acts as compartmentalization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tu WeiMing Circles of Concern</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-tu-weiming-confucian-circles-of-concern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-tu-weiming-confucian-circles-of-concern/</guid>
      <description>source:: Tu Weiming | Internet Encyclopedia of Philosophy
Vaguely remembered from HASS classes, the center of the circle is the self, and outside of that is the family (people that you owe responsibility to?) and then outside of that is the world?
I remember that this is linked to the idea of Individualism as self and other circle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why create content</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-why-create-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-why-create-content/</guid>
      <description>Why do I want to create content (youtube, blog)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zettel Inbox</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-zettel-inbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-zettel-inbox/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ll put any zettels that I want to create (maybe) here, currently I am going through some digital gardens ([List of digital gardens from obsidian roundup](https://lukerambling.de/gardens/)) and I think some of them resonate tho I have different interpretations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caution note for using dropbox and obsidian sync</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-caution-note-for-using-dropbox-and-obsidian-sync/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-caution-note-for-using-dropbox-and-obsidian-sync/</guid>
      <description>How to use both dropbox and obsidian sync so that you don&amp;#39;t get weird missing files</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Keyboard Layout - Colemakdh</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-colemak-dh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-colemak-dh/</guid>
      <description>How I learnt to type on the colemak dh layout and my experience with this keyboard layout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Setup for Working in Bed</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-my-working-in-bed-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-my-working-in-bed-setup/</guid>
      <description>Intro If you work from home then you probably have tried to work in bed before :) but it is rather uncomfortable with a tiny laptop and suspending an actual monitor right above my face is a bit scary (it might drop&amp;hellip; directly onto my head) so my current solution is: a projector!
Downsides of a projector? It is super loud.
Basic Setup You need:
a projector (hdmi input) that is hopefully not too loud some computer (can be headless like the mac mini) if the computer does not have a hdmi slot then you also need a dongle mouse or even a trackball split keyboard (two parts of keyboard attached by cable) cables computer to projector (hdmi to hdmi) keyboard to computer (USB C to USB C for moonlander) - this needs to be a long cable (1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>don&#39;t be perfect just do it</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-dont-be-perfect-just-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-dont-be-perfect-just-do-it/</guid>
      <description>The idea that you shouldn&amp;#39;t aim so high because then you won&amp;#39;t do anything - practice makes perfect aiming for quality in the beginning is dumb</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>failure is the mother of success</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-failure-is-the-mother-of-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-failure-is-the-mother-of-success/</guid>
      <description>source::
“Laziness is the mother of all bad habits, but ultimately she is a mother and we should respect her” - Shikamaru Nara
&amp;ldquo;Failure is the mother of success&amp;rdquo; is a common saying and from my experiences it seems pretty true that we learn best from experimenting and trying out things for ourselves bz-we learn best from doing - especially from our mistakes (because we remember better and actually understand) - see I hear and I forget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frame it to form Preferences</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-frame-it-to-form-preferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-frame-it-to-form-preferences/</guid>
      <description>Source People often don&amp;rsquo;t know what frame they want for the family portrait, so they go to the shop and the assistant will put up various different frames against the picture so you can see what it looks like. Then people are able to voice their preferences like &amp;ldquo;not this one, but similar, I want a lighter wood frame&amp;rdquo;
source:: David Perell
Reflection We often think that we don&amp;rsquo;t have preferences or opinions on something until we actually encounter the topic and interact with it (able to frame it in our head), then we have loads of opinions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hear and I forget. I see and I remember. I do and I understand</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-i-hear-and-i-forget.-i-see-and-i-remember.-i-do-and-i-understand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-i-hear-and-i-forget.-i-see-and-i-remember.-i-do-and-i-understand/</guid>
      <description>source:: etymology - Origin of &amp;ldquo;I hear and I forget. I see and I remember. I do and I understand.&amp;rdquo;? - English Language &amp;amp; Usage Stack Exchange This is a pretty common saying and this links to a really interesting discussion on what is the origin of this saying.
Meaning: bz-we learn best from doing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>note-blogging</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-note-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-note-blogging/</guid>
      <description>source:: A note blog by Alexkehayias - Reflections on Two Years of Note Blogging
About What is note blogging?
The idea that you should publish the notes you are writing instead of waiting for them to become fully formed blog posts.
Reflections I like this practice because I often take a lot of notes on a topic but then never actually get to publishing the blogpost / video because getting something to &amp;lsquo;production ready&amp;rsquo; is really hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rubber ducky problem solving</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-rubber-ducky-problem-solving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-rubber-ducky-problem-solving/</guid>
      <description>source::
A way programmers problem solve (try to understand why their code is not working) is to explain the problem to a rubber ducky, because the process of explaining to &amp;ldquo;someone&amp;rdquo; really helps find issues that we mentally brush over when we explain to ourselves (because we assume that we know everything about it already).
Hence we should z-express to think through the idea and z-write for other people in order to be better thinkers, you dont think in your head you only think when you actually express the idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vulnerability brings people closer</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-vulnerability-brings-people-closer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-vulnerability-brings-people-closer/</guid>
      <description>source:: some ted talk? I am looking for it &amp;gt;..&amp;lt; she spoke about how she found vulnerability was important to forming meaningful relationships</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MetaPicker Template in Obsidian</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-metapicker-template-in-obsidian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-metapicker-template-in-obsidian/</guid>
      <description>Status This is the script for my meta-template picker video Obsidian: Building the Meta-Templater from Scratch - YouTube.
Currently working on this blog post
Post Today I want to share, how to use a meta-templater in your workflow
so first, What is the meta-templater
(what it does - trigger template based on name of the file) Bryan Jenks
Bryan Jenks first coined this term, he adds this symbol in front of his links so it tells obsidian what kind of note this is supposed to be, so example a book source note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Tester</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/private/css-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/private/css-tester/</guid>
      <description>A page to test css on my blog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar Priority Alignment</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/zcon-calendar-priority-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/zcon-calendar-priority-alignment/</guid>
      <description>A writeup of how I do my weekly review in obsidian</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I consume content and auto collect notes</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-how-i-consume-content-and-auto-collect-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-how-i-consume-content-and-auto-collect-notes/</guid>
      <description>TODO Video link here
sources of where I get content external discord obsidian, obsidian forums fiction - inspired thinking articles - david perell essays anything of interest shortform newsletters blogs - elizabeth book notes courses papers → zotero → pdf highlights (can make a seperate post on this) - can highlight on mac or on ipad and send back keeping track of my own experiments in obsidian what do I do Focus on auto collection as much as possible - I tried like putting it in notes apps but having to process takes a lot of time (curation vs convenience) highlight the thing auto collected by readwise mac: hypothesis for articles, videos just write in obsidian ipad: command browser android: twitter is readwise, snipd for podcast notes braintoss to daily note iphone: braintoss → email → my script android: braintoss ipad: braintoss process in obsidian things I am exploring pkm thinking tools scrintal logseq - like it but also outliners not good for export to other people link to video comparing the 3 for zettelkasten purposes apps read it later apps (instapaper) - but I have command browser on ipad which is a one time purchase kindles I actually don&amp;rsquo;t really read books that much?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>make the crappy first draft</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-make-the-crappy-first-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-make-the-crappy-first-draft/</guid>
      <description>source::
Source Reference &amp;amp; Literature Note: Quote + Author Info / Link
Ali Abdaal often talks about making your first crappy 100 videos or telling himself to just write out the crappy first draft of his book.
David Perell also mentioned how you need to get started with something crappy then you can figure out what you want like Frame it to form Preferences you only have preferences when you can see the thing e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Weekly Review in Obsidian</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-automated-weekly-review-in-obsidian/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/posts/my-blogpost-automated-weekly-review-in-obsidian/</guid>
      <description>A writeup of how I do my weekly review in obsidian</description>
    </item>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/pages/newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/pages/newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Some place holder text
Do a fancy phone thing + some nice border + some archived newsletters and signup email form</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
