<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Zettelkasten on Pamela Wang</title>
    <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zettelkasten on Pamela Wang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://caffa.github.io/zettels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>don&#39;t be perfect just do it</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-dont-be-perfect-just-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-dont-be-perfect-just-do-it/</guid>
      <description>The idea that you shouldn&amp;#39;t aim so high because then you won&amp;#39;t do anything - practice makes perfect aiming for quality in the beginning is dumb</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>failure is the mother of success</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-failure-is-the-mother-of-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-failure-is-the-mother-of-success/</guid>
      <description>source::
“Laziness is the mother of all bad habits, but ultimately she is a mother and we should respect her” - Shikamaru Nara
&amp;ldquo;Failure is the mother of success&amp;rdquo; is a common saying and from my experiences it seems pretty true that we learn best from experimenting and trying out things for ourselves bz-we learn best from doing - especially from our mistakes (because we remember better and actually understand) - see Z - I hear and I forget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frame it to form Preferences</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-frame-it-to-form-preferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-frame-it-to-form-preferences/</guid>
      <description>Source People often don&amp;rsquo;t know what frame they want for the family portrait, so they go to the shop and the assistant will put up various different frames against the picture so you can see what it looks like. Then people are able to voice their preferences like &amp;ldquo;not this one, but similar, I want a lighter wood frame&amp;rdquo;
source:: David Perell
Reflection We often think that we don&amp;rsquo;t have preferences or opinions on something until we actually encounter the topic and interact with it (able to frame it in our head), then we have loads of opinions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hear and I forget. I see and I remember. I do and I understand</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-i-hear-and-i-forget.-i-see-and-i-remember.-i-do-and-i-understand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-i-hear-and-i-forget.-i-see-and-i-remember.-i-do-and-i-understand/</guid>
      <description>source:: etymology - Origin of &amp;ldquo;I hear and I forget. I see and I remember. I do and I understand.&amp;rdquo;? - English Language &amp;amp; Usage Stack Exchange This is a pretty common saying and this links to a really interesting discussion on what is the origin of this saying.
Meaning: bz-we learn best from doing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>note-blogging</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-note-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-note-blogging/</guid>
      <description>source:: A note blog by Alexkehayias - Reflections on Two Years of Note Blogging
About What is note blogging?
The idea that you should publish the notes you are writing instead of waiting for them to become fully formed blog posts.
Reflections I like this practice because I often take a lot of notes on a topic but then never actually get to publishing the blogpost / video because getting something to &amp;lsquo;production ready&amp;rsquo; is really hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rubber ducky problem solving</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-rubber-ducky-problem-solving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-rubber-ducky-problem-solving/</guid>
      <description>source::
A way programmers problem solve (try to understand why their code is not working) is to explain the problem to a rubber ducky, because the process of explaining to &amp;ldquo;someone&amp;rdquo; really helps find issues that we mentally brush over when we explain to ourselves (because we assume that we know everything about it already).
Hence we should z-express to think through the idea and z-write for other people in order to be better thinkers, Z - you dont think in your head you only think when you actually express the idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vulnerability brings people closer</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-vulnerability-brings-people-closer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-vulnerability-brings-people-closer/</guid>
      <description>source:: some ted talk? I am looking for it &amp;gt;..&amp;lt; she spoke about how she found vulnerability was important to forming meaningful relationships</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar Priority Alignment</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/zcon-calendar-priority-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/zcon-calendar-priority-alignment/</guid>
      <description>A writeup of how I do my weekly review in obsidian</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>make the crappy first draft</title>
      <link>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-make-the-crappy-first-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caffa.github.io/zettels/z-make-the-crappy-first-draft/</guid>
      <description>source::
Source Reference &amp;amp; Literature Note: Quote + Author Info / Link
Ali Abdaal often talks about making your first crappy 100 videos or telling himself to just write out the crappy first draft of his book.
David Perell also mentioned how you need to get started with something crappy then you can figure out what you want like Frame it to form Preferences you only have preferences when you can see the thing e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
